Here. This is Master Claude's hair.
来 这是库洛德大人的头发
Appreciate it.
好好珍惜
Demon King. It's indeed Demon King's hair.
魔王 的确是魔王的头发
Demon King! Demon King!
魔王大人 魔王大人
Demon King! It's the Demon King!
魔王 是魔王
There's a hint of Demon King's scent.
有一点点的魔王气息
Don't worry. Master Claude and I...
你们放心吧 我会跟库洛德大人…
It's too late to change anything now.
生米煮成熟饭
You... Can you be more gentle with the Demon King?
你…可不可以对魔王大人温柔点
The priority is to maintain the marriage.
首要任务是维持婚约
Love can be cultivated when things are done.
爱这种东西 到手后再好好培养即可
Anyway, he'll be mine as long as he falls in love with me.
总之 让他爱上我后他就是我的了
From a different perspective,
换个立场想想
love like this is like standing on a cliff.
这种爱简直就像站在悬崖上
That's right.
没错
It's to convince him to jump
就是要拼命怂恿他往下跳
or even push him down
甚至是推他一把
so he'll never get up again.
让他永远爬不上来
I'M THE VILLAINESS, SO I'M TAMING THE FINAL BOSS
《因为是反派大小姐》 《所以养了魔王》
Master Claude is going out on an inspection?
库洛德大人要出巡视察
"THE VILLAINESS' LOVE IS UNREQUITED" That's right.
(反派大小姐的爱传递不出去) 没错
Demon King losing his memory and magic is no longer a secret.
魔王大人失去记忆和魔力的事 已经公诸于世了吧
That is why he is going for an inspection.
所以才会让他去视察吧
The objective is to make a good impression on the people.
目的是加深人民对他的好印象
Master Cedric and Miss Lilia will go along too.
塞多利克王子和莉莉安小姐 也会一同前去
They're going too?
他们也一起去
It was Miss Lilia who arranged the inspection this time.
不过这次的视察 是莉莉安小姐安排的
If it's Miss Lilia's arrangement...
既然是莉莉安小姐安排的…
This is the game's world.
这里是游戏里的世界哦
Then, she could have possibly started the game.
那她很可能开启游戏事件
Elephas.
艾雷法斯
If you'd recover Master Claude's memories, what would you do?
若你要让库洛德大人恢复记忆 你会怎么做
Well... Show him things that could help him remember the past.
这个嘛… 会给他看能想起过去记忆的事物
He didn't remember me after seeing me.
可是就算我见到他 他也没想起来
It made me feel hurt.
让我有点受伤
If I may be so bold to speak, I believe this is to be expected.
恕我僭越 但这是理所当然的
As the owner of the Holy Sword, Lady Aileen,
爱琳小姐是圣剑之主
your affinity with Master Claude's memory is poor.
会阻碍库洛德大人恢复记忆
Is it because of the "Holy" nature of the Holy Sword?
因为…圣剑是"圣属性"吗
Yes. I believe Master Claude's memory is perhaps related to magic.
是的 我认为库洛德大人的记忆 或许跟魔力有关连
Encountering demons should rouse his magic and make them a better stimulus.
见到魔物 比较能刺激他 唤醒魔力和记忆
Indeed. Master Claude has a deep connection with the demons.
有道理 库洛德大人 和魔物们的感情很深厚
Speaking of demons, there are reports of demons sightings on the streets.
说到魔物 有情报指出 在街道上偶尔会看到到魔物出没
They're risking themselves coming out of the jungle to look for Master Claude.
它们一定是为了寻找库洛德大人 才冒险从森林出来的吧
Which also means, this inspection is related to the demons.
也就是说 这次的视察 是跟魔物有关的事件
By the way,
对了
this is from Doni. He says it's a blueprint.
这是多尼给的 说是设计图
Thank you.
谢谢
Isaac, what are you making?
艾札克 你要做什么
Well, this and that, just in case.
以防万一的东西
What plans do you have next?
你接下来有什么打算
I'll infiltrate Master Claude's inspection.
混进库洛德大人的视察队伍中
Which is why Master Claude,
所以呢 库洛德大人
please keep it a secret if you see me during the inspection next week.
下星期在视察时看到我的话 请记得帮我保密哦
I... refuse.
我…我拒绝
I was about to say, what are you up to bursting in from the terrace?
我还想说你突然从阳台闯进来 要做什么
It's been three days.
三天不见了
What are you doing?
你干什么啦
Things a fiancee will do.
做未婚妻可以做的事啊
I'm going to break off the engagement.
我打算解除婚约了
Before you break it off, I will make it so your body can't live without me.
在你解除之前 我会让你养成 没有我就不行的身体
Master Claude, I brought you apple pie.
库洛德大人 今天我带了苹果派哦
I don't need it.
不需要
What are you reading?
你在看什么
It has nothing to do with you.
跟你无关
This is fun.
真好玩
I don't think it's fun at all.
我一点都不觉得好玩
This is the first time I'm having unrequited love. It feels amazing.
这可是我初次的单恋 感觉真不错
Master Claude. Are you awake?
库洛德大人 你起床了吗
Stay there and don't come out.
待在里面别出来
Master Claude. How are you feeling?
库洛德大人 感觉还好吗
What brought both of you here?
两位 有什么事吗
We are here to tell you about the changes to the inspection's schedule.
我们来告诉你 视察行程有所变更
I made some cookies.
我做了饼干
Please have them.
请吃吧
That basket... Is there a snack in there?
那个篮子… 里面放了点心吗
That's...
那是…
I had the maids prepare them.
是我拜托仆人们准备的
If only you had told me earlier.
如果早点告诉我就好了
What am I going to do with the cookies?
这些饼干怎么办
Since you prepared them, let me enjoy them.
你特地准备的 让我品尝吧
Can you also make some tea?
也能请你帮忙泡杯茶吗
No problem.
没问题
He didn't want my apple pie just now.
他刚刚明明就不要我的苹果派
Regarding the inspection,
关于视察的事情
there have been a lot of demons sighted in the imperial capital.
最近皇都内出现许多魔物
Demons?
魔物
Don't worry. We will have the Holy Knights' apprentices coming along.
放心吧 我们会让 骑士团见习生担任护卫
Even if demons were to come out, they're just small fries.
就算魔物出现 也只是些小角色
I'll be trying out the dress for the inspection.
我得去试穿视察时的礼服
It's almost time for me to go.
差不多该走了
Don't you have to go with her, Cedric?
塞多利克不用跟着去吗
No. I'll rest a bit more.
不了 我再休息一下
Oh, Master Claude. You haven't had any cookies, right?
对了库洛德大人 你还没吃饼干吧
Taste one.
吃一口看看嘛
Here.
来
Lilia, Cedric is here too.
莉莉安 塞多利克也在场
Don't make him misunderstand.
别做些会令人误会的举动
But, I'll call you brother-in-law one day, anyway.
可是 总有一天我得称呼你王兄
So, Cedric won't be mad.
所以塞多利克不会生气的
Right?
对吧
Lilia, brother is a modest man.
莉莉安 王兄为人谦逊
Don't trouble him.
别让王兄感到困扰
All right.
好吧
Master Claude, I will come again to see you.
那么库洛德大人 我会再来探望你的
She's still the same. Trying to court another's fiancee.
她还是一样 擅自对别人的未婚夫出手
Brother. I feel so sorry
王兄 不好意思
that Lilia said such things.
莉莉安说了这么任性的话
What?
干嘛
It's fine. Since Cedric has already noticed anyway.
没关系 反正塞多利克大人已经发现了
Is that so?
是这样吗
I just thought the basket looked familiar.
我只是觉得那个篮子很眼熟
As expected of Miss Lilia.
不愧是莉莉安小姐
The cookies are good, Master Claude.
库洛德大人 饼干很美味哦
Is that so?
是吗…
I'm going back now.
我要回去了
What? Why are you giving it to me?
干嘛 为什么给我
Wastes will always go to the waste bins.
垃圾要丢到垃圾桶里
Waste... Wait. Are you calling me a waste bin?
垃圾… 等等 你说我是垃圾桶吗
Master Claude. Next time, I will bring better cookies.
库洛德大人 下次我会带比这个更美味的饼干来
You don't have to.
你不用带来
See you during the inspection.
我们视察时见吧
Wait. Are you serious about coming...
慢着 你真的要来吗…
Did you learn anything?
有什么收获吗
I learned how it hurts in unrequited love.
我知道单恋之苦了
Forgive me for being presumptuous,
恕我僭越
but Master Claude should see the look on your face now.
你现在露出的表情 应该给库洛德大人看吧
Men are weak to women's tears.
男人最怕看见女人落泪了
Never. I don't intend to win him over with tears.
不要 我才不想靠眼泪掳获他
Aileen. It's bad.
爱琳 不好了
Fight! A fight!
吵架 吵架
I want you to return it to me.
我要你还给我
I can't. This is Demon Snuff.
不能还你 这可是魔香耶
You're annoying. Give it back to me.
烦死了 快还给我
Why are you always in the imperial castle?
你为什么会在皇都
It was agreed that you would not leave Mirchetta.
当初说好的条件是不准离开米尔契塔
That's why Master Claude let you go.
库洛德大人才放过你的吧
It's none of your business. This has nothing to do with you.
要你管 这件事跟你无关
-Of course it does. Don't break your promise. -Have they been like this?
-当然有关好吗 不能毁约 -他们一直这样吗
-Auguste was patrolling -You're annoying. Give it back.
-奥古斯特在巡逻时 -烦死了 快还我
-and saw her by chance so he brought her here. -I said never.
-偶然在皇城遇到她 就把她带来了 -就说了不能还
Are you done?
你闹够了没
Know your place!
你可不可以安分点
It has been a while, Selena.
塞蕾娜 好久不见
Aileen Lauren Dautriche.
爱琳 罗伦 多德勒
You're the last person I want to meet.
我最不想看见你
Are you here at the capital to see Master Cedric?
你来皇都 是为了见塞多利克大人吗
You must be here in search of support, right?
你应该是为了寻求后盾才来此的吧
First of all, it must be Miss Lilia who was once related to you that you're coming for.
首先想依赖的 就是曾与你有关的莉莉安小姐
Next, it must be her fiance, Master Cedric.
再来就是她的未婚夫 塞多利克大人
Master Cedric has the ability to protect the status of women and their future.
有能力保障女性的地位及将来
You're good at your plots, becoming a mistress is also possible.
你这么善于算计 弄到个妃妾的位置也很有可能
You sound like you know me.
你真懂我
You're indeed the ex-fiancee.
不愧是前未婚妻
Mistress... It can't be.
妃妾… 不会吧
I'll marry a rich man after my graduation, anyway.
反正我毕业后 注定要嫁给某个暴发户贵族
I just want to marry someone rich and in power. What is wrong with that?
我只是想嫁给更有钱有势的人 有什么不对了
It's true. It's worth a shot.
有道理 的确值得放手一搏
Thanks for your understanding.
感谢你的理解
Can you let me go now?
可以放我回去了吧
Auguste. Return everything to her, except the Demon Snuff.
奥古斯特 除了魔香之外 其他东西都还给她吧
But...
可是…
Selena. If you have any intelligence you wish to provide, send me a message.
塞蕾娜 若想卖情报给我的话 就传个信息过来
I can give you what you want.
我可以给你你所想要的东西
I'll walk you out.
我送你离开吧
Whatever.
随便你
Auguste. Is this going to be all right?
奥古斯特 这样好吗
I don't know.
我都不知道
She'll get married right after graduation...
原来她毕业后 就必须立刻嫁人…
Everyone has their own story.
每个人都有自己的故事
If you care about everything, there won't be an end to it.
全部都在意的话 会没完没了的
Actually, I think she is being silly.
其实 我一直觉得她很傻
She's always playing nice in school in front of others.
在学时 总是在大家面前扮演好人
But, I guess she is trying very hard too.
不过 她应该也是很拼命的吧
Since you know that, you should face her.
既然知道这点 那就更应该面对她
Yes. You're right.
是啊 你说得没错
I'll look for her.
我去找她
You used to respect Miss Lilia so much but you're trying to court her husband now.
你曾那么尊敬莉莉安小姐 却想对她的未婚夫出手
It's because this is about my life. It's only natural to do that.
事关自己的人生 会这么做很正常吧
Initially, I wanted to ask the Holy Sword Maiden for help.
一开始 我也想拜托圣剑少女
But...
不过…
Is that woman trouble?
那女人很碍事吗
No. It's just bothering me.
不是的 只是觉得很困扰
I couldn't tell what the woman was up to.
我完全看不出那女人的底细
Wouldn't it be dangerous to try to get her fiance then?
你还想对她的未婚夫出手 会不会太危险了
I have nothing else to lose anymore.
我已经没什么可失去的了
Selena!
塞蕾娜
Let me send you back.
还是我送你回去吧
I have to apologize to you.
我得跟你道歉
Even though I can't forgive you for what you did to James.
虽然 我还无法原谅 你对赛姆斯做的事
If you can't forgive me, why are you here?
既然无法原谅还来找我干嘛
Are you trying to show that you're kind?
想表现其实你很温柔吗
No...
不是的…
Don't come after me anymore. I'm disgusted by you.
别再来找我了 看到你就觉得恶心
ELEPHAS LEVI CV UCHIYAMA KOKI
(艾雷法斯 雷比) (CV 内山昂辉)
THE LAST DESCENDANT OF LEVI, THE MAGIC GRAND DUKES
(魔法大公雷比一族的末裔)
THE LEVI TRIBE IS SEEN AS A TRIBE WITH DANGEROUS MAGIC
(雷比一族被视为) (拥有危险魔力的族群)
THE KINGDOM HELD HOSTAGES OF THE YOUNG AND OLD AND COERCED THEM INTO BECOMING
(皇国把幼童和老人当人质) (强制他们成为)
THE MAGE THAT PROTECTS THE ROYAL FAMILY ELMIR WHO ARE ACTIVE IN THE DARK
(守护艾路梅亚皇族的魔导士) (并在暗中活跃)
These apprentices are going to escort Your Highness's carriage.
这些骑士见习生 将守护殿下的马车
Raise your heads, all of you.
全员 抬起头来
This is Aili Kahlua.
这位是艾里 加尔亚
He'll take command of the entire unit.
负责指挥整体队伍
Take command... Don't tell me, is she the captain?
指挥… 她该不会是队长吧
No... I mean he...
不…我说他…
Yes.
是的
He's strong and can bring down the Holy Knights alone.
他的实力很强 有能力一人击败整个骑士团
Alone?
一人击败…
It's said that he'll have a bright future.
听说将来大有前途
Bright future...
大有前途…
Aili Kahlua. Escort Your Highness to the carriage.
艾里 加尔亚 带殿下上马车
The rest of you, get ready for departure.
其他人 准备出发
Yes!
是
Your Highness. This way, please.
殿下 这边请
What are you doing?
你在干嘛
You'll be executed if you meet me.
擅自见我会被处以极刑吧
As long as Master Claude and I have an engagement
只要库洛德大人继续与我维持婚约
I won't be executed.
我就不会被处以极刑
Are you threatening me?
你在威胁我吗
Go back, now.
现在立刻给我回去
I don't want to have anything to do with you.
我不想再跟你扯上关系了
Brother. It's pointless for you to say that
王兄 就算你这么说也没用
because this is the type of woman she is.
因为她就是这种女人
Hurry up and return to your post.
快点回到岗位上
Do you want me to unmask you?
你想被拆穿吗
Try it if you dare.
有种就试试看啊
This time, I will plunge you into the depths of hell.
这次我会把你踢下十八层地狱
What are you saying?
你说什么
You must have hidden Selena in a safe place, right?
反正你已经把塞蕾娜 藏在安全的地方了吧
Selena? What are you talking about?
塞蕾娜 你在说什么
You can pretend all you want.
要装傻就随你便
I'm just blabbering.
反正我只是在自言自语
Blabbering to a talking waste bin.
对着会说话的垃圾桶喃喃自语
You... What do you think I am?
你…这阵子你到底把我当什么
You two have a good relationship.
你们的感情真好
It must be weird for me to be here.
有我在场会很别扭吧
I'm leaving.
先走了
But, Master Claude.
可是 库洛德大人
Don't come near me.
不要靠近我
You're still the same as always.
你还是跟以前一样
Naturally, Brother would feel uncomfortable.
王兄会感到不安也很正常
Master Claude feels uncomfortable?
库洛德大人 感到不安
Miss Aileen. The carriage is about to leave.
爱琳小姐 马车要出发了
All right. How is the plan?
好 作战计划安排得如何
Yes. It's just as planned.
是 按照计划进行
Besides, I found the person in charge of this inspection too.
另外 我也查到此次视察的负责人了
Person in charge? Isn't it Master Cedric?
负责人 不是塞多利克大人吗
It's a high government official named Leister Craine.
是一位高官 名叫列斯塔 克莱茵
He appears to have planned the routes as well.
视察路径 也是他策划的
Leister...
列斯塔…
I remember he is a character that can be tamed from the first game.
我记得 他是1的攻略角色
A calm and levelheaded strategist.
是位冷静沉着的参谋角色
Which also means, Miss Lilia who is also familiar with the game
也就是说 熟知游戏内容的莉莉安小姐
has tamed him.
已经攻略过他了
It seems I have to stay away from Aileen Lauren Dautriche.
看来 还是该远离爱琳罗伦多德勒
She is related to my past.
她跟我的过去有关连
Master Claude. Sorry for making you wait.
库洛德大人 让你久等了
Where is Cedric?
塞多利克呢
He's not feeling well.
他觉得身体不太舒服
He plans to rest in the castle today.
今天打算在城堡里休息
Is it fine that you're not with him?
你不陪在他身边好吗
And being alone with a man who is not your fiance...
跟非未婚夫的男性单独相处…
It's all right.
没关系
Master Claude and I are going to be family one day.
我跟库洛德大人 总有一天会成为一家人的
Do you feel bored being with me?
跟我在一起 觉得很无聊吗
No. I just think that I'm unreliable.
不 我只是觉得 自己很不可靠
Why are you saying that?
你说什么傻话
You just have to stay the way you are
你保持这样就行了
because you're an important person.
因为你是重要的人
What?
什么
I've never heard that a carriage could be lifted like that...
我没听说马车会被抬起…
Lilia!
莉莉安
Demon in front. Return Master Claude.
前方的魔物 把库洛德大人还来
Return. You. No way.
回去 你 不行
Save the Demon King!
拯救魔王
Protect the Demon King!
保护魔王
Is he talking about me?
他说的是我吗
Almond. Lure this one to the plaza.
杏仁 就这样引诱它到广场
We'll catch him there.
在那里抓住他
Got it.
收到
Unit One, follow me.
第一部队 跟着我
Fenrir Unit, chase the humans away.
芬里尔部队 赶走人类
Holy Sword.
圣剑
Where's Master Claude?
库洛德大人呢
Miss Aileen.
爱琳小姐
-Protect His Highness. -Yes!
-保护殿下 -是
Do not shoot!
不准射击
Shoot!
射击
They are saved.
得…得救了
Hold it.
先别动手
Everyone, take the demon away.
各位 快点带走魔物
It seems like we don't need the sedatives.
看来 不需要使用镇定剂了
It's larger than imagined.
比想象中的巨大
Next, let's take them to the castle.
接下来 送他们回皇城就好了吧
Yes. Protecting him under the Holy Knight's name can protect his reputation.
对 以圣骑士团保护他的名义 这样才能保住面子
Very clever.
很聪明
This is a small matter.
这点小事 理所当然
Put them down.
把他们放下来吧
How troublesome.
伤脑筋
Demon King!
魔王大人 魔王大人
Save. Demon King.
拯救 魔王
No.
不行
Don't hurt the humans. Retreat.
不准伤害人类 退下
But... the Demon King's wishes...
可是…魔王的期望…
What are you talking about?
你在说什么
It seems like I should stay away from Aileen Lauren Dautriche.
看来 还是该远离爱琳罗伦多德勒
You.
你
You're in the Demon King's way. Be gone.
你是魔王的阻碍 消失吧
The hearts of the demon and Demon King are connected.
魔物 与魔王心意相通
So, this means...
所以 这句话是…
I don't need you. Be gone.
不需要你 消失吧
I'm... the woman who is not needed?
我是…不被需要的女人
Be gone!
消失吧
Aili. What are you doing?
艾里 你在干嘛
Walt! Lyle!
沃鲁特 凯鲁
Kill it!
杀了它
No way!
不行
Master Claude would be very sad.
库洛德大人 会很伤心的
What a fool.
愚蠢
Treating the Demon King's intention as an order.
竟然错把魔王的心意当成命令
Demon King. We will do as you wish.
魔王 我们会遵照您所愿
If the Demon King doesn't need us,
若魔王认为不需要我们
we will disappear before you.
我们便会从您面前消失
Master Claude is so obsessed with me that you'd have the demons dispose of me.
库洛德大人 如此在意我 在意到让魔物来解决我
-I... I didn't... -Smile.
-我…我没有… -笑啊
Just as you always do.
跟以往一样
I know this is only my unrequited love.
我知道 这只是我的单恋
I have misunderstood.
是我会错意
But...
可是…
If I've causing you trouble, I will leave!
如果真的碍到你了 我消失便是
I will not go to the ball too.
我也不会去参加舞会了